{
    "id": "c448029433ca4e61b7d2fd6f06aa1bba",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Paper ………………… wood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is made by",
                "is made with",
                "is made from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d171f40ea5804bc7a96e62d5f61f2f82"
        },
        {
            "question": "The car ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is still fixed",
                "is still being fixed",
                "has fixed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7bfbac26403144ecb8454399d5adde43"
        },
        {
            "question": "This bucket ……………………… plastic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is made from",
                "is made with",
                "is made of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c4d7c2af87df4c79b629320d988364d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ……………………… by the teacher.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has punished",
                "was punished",
                "is punished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "120423f898884770b79636779c4c7f38"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thieves …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have caught",
                "have been caught",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f70157063f6c46328cab0c5614d7365a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you think the roof ………………… by evening?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is repaired",
                "will be repaired",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d36526eaec87496787956cc7c2c36d6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tablet …………………… .. with food.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must take",
                "must be taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39871e72c53f46069f068555d0a3a1bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The payment ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has sent",
                "has been sent",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b23f89f98f40426b9a4d7f3233fd6c3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The parcel …………………… by courier this morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is sent",
                "was sent",
                "has sent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bb8b061407d34af588e3e4185ac3ab6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The matter …………………….. now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is discussed",
                "is being discussed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bde60c5f3044436a978b7c0b89b3d196"
        }
    ]
}